all right so good to be here with you
guys thanks for coming
out okay all
right listen I don't know if you guys
have ever noticed this but every once in
a while I will meet somebody who is
really good friends with both of their
parents I think that's a little
weird that is an either or
situation you're only supposed to get
one parent who you're really close to
who's super accepting and loving and
supportive and the other
one is your
dad he's just a guy with a seatat
machine doing his best
I think a lot of people might guess from
looking at me that the only drug I
abused is
melatonin and they'd be right I don't
know that much about drugs but a friend
of mine told me the other day that he
just read this
study and
scientists
proved that sugar is more addicting than
cocaine and and I was like that's super
interesting it's also probably the least
helpful
information that's ever been
discovered I don't really know what they
want us to do with that
data there's not a lot of practical
takeaways unless they're recommending
that we substitute sugar with
cocaine I think it's a bad idea
yeah imagine I show up to family dinner
on Sunday I'm like hey everyone I made
my famous crack
cookies you guys are never going to
guess the healthy ingredient swap that I
made I bet you can't even taste the
difference but you will feel
it I don't know I can already hear the
YouTube Fitness influencers they're on
their Channel they're like I love this
new diet ever since I started eating
cocaine instead of sugar I have so much
energy this video is sponsored by the
cartel I feel like that would be like
discovering that milk is more fattening
than bleach
what are we doing
here I don't
know to be perfectly Frank I do not
believe that sugar is more addicting
than
cocaine I don't know if you guys know
anybody with a drug
problem but I
do you're better off with
sugar I have never met anybody in my
life whose parents had to kick them out
of the house and were like
listen we love you but your sweet tooth
is tearing this family
apart stick in with Skittles
so I'm a marketer that's my day
job and because of that I like to pay
attention to ads that I see out in the
wild and I was driving other day I saw
an ad it said a world without
elephants is unimaginable
and I was like that is so
weird because it is super easy to
imagine a world without
elephants I do it every
day here's how you do it think of the
world take out the
elephants okay it's not that hard I can
do it right now if I just close my eyes
I did it
it's so natural okay and maybe I'm
unusual in this but elephants haven't
really played a big role in my
life they haven't been a big influence
on me I think I'd be the same person
have the same values everything if the
elephants weren't
here basically I have a hard time
imagining a scenario one day where i'm
like
well maybe if the elephants were still
here I wouldn't be in this gang right
now I'm not anti- elephant okay I'm just
anti- elephant
propaganda I think flirting is a talent
I think it's a skill just like anything
else some people are very good at it
anytime any place they can turn on the
charm I'm not one of those people I went
on a date with a guy a while back and I
was very nervous because I thought he
was super cute but it went really well
until the end when he
said so how come you're not married
yet and I was like oh
well I'm actually
divorced but it was kind of a weird
thing to
say because
I am not
divorced but I was like this will be fun
and
flirty and he said wow I'm really sorry
to hear that and I was like oh he
actually thinks I'm
divorced probably cuz I told him that
I didn't really know where to go from
there so I
said we had a kid
together that wasn't
true he's like man that's got to be
really tough and I was like okay he
still does not understand that I'm
coming on to
him so I had to lay on even
thicker I said yeah things didn't really
work out with the baby
either so I donated it to
Goodwill at that point my date realized
I was
kidding he also realized why I was still
single so it came together in the
end not my forte for
sure I did see a statistic the other
day on Tik Tok and
I'll be so honest it said that my
chances of marrying a guy who is above 6
feet tall who also makes over 100k a
year is
like
2% it's not good
okay but I'm actually dating a guy right
now who is 6'
five thank you
and once he gets a
job I'm hoping to beat those
odds it's not looking good for the time
being and I don't need the guy that I'm
dating to have Deep Pockets but my
boyfriend has those little tiny Pockets
that are like sewn
shut they're just for
looks kind of like my boyfriend so
yeah uh one opinion that I have
is I don't think that professional
bowlers deserve
respect
okay because like most people I go
bowling about one once a year with some
friends mostly is a
joke but without fail at least once
during the game I will get a
strike mostly on
accident if I can do the best move in
your
sport with no
effort you are not talented
you're just not
okay I can't do the best move in any
other sport I've never gone ice skating
with my buddies on a Friday night and
accidentally landed a triple
axle and been like whoa that was really
lucky it's just bulling
another controversial opinion I don't
think people with ADHD should be allowed
to
drive maybe not on board with me but
hang in there because listen the number
one rule of the road is don't drive
distracted and people with ADHD cannot
do that okay it's not their fault but
they still can't do that and on top of
that every person I have ever met with
with ADHD is
like yeah I don't take my meds
anymore they all quit I don't understand
why but I was asking my brother about
the other day cuz he has ADHD and I was
like why don't you take your Aderall and
he said I just really didn't like how it
changed my
personality and I was
like so it
worked your personality is dangerous
I hate dishwashers as
well anybody else
or all right maybe I'm alone but here's
the thing
dishwashers should work a lot better
than they
do they just never work and we have the
technology to do it I know we do because
if you look at other appliances like the
refrigerator the refrigerator is highly
effective okay okay and they're getting
more and more bells and whistles all the
time they'll send you notifications
they've got sensors they've got cameras
and touchscreens and I'm like okay
that's awesome that my fridge can mine
Bitcoin but I just want a clean cup
okay I think of the dishwasher as The
Village
Idiot of kitchen
appliances all right because the
microwave kills it every time no notes
the oven impeccable track record and
then you get to the dishwasher and it's
like I know I was supposed to get the
cereal off of this
bowl but
instead I super glued them
together I hope that's
okay it's
not it's
infuriating and there's a lot of
dishwasher apologists out there okay cuz
people will say things to me like no no
it works you just have to clean
everything off
first like what are you talking about
that's the entire Point like evidently
the dishwasher sucks at dishwashing but
it's amazing at
brainwashing I just wish everybody could
just admit and accept that we're
handwashing and then we're putting our
dishes in their own little water
park it's
fine I have a couple of Roommates
unfortunately they're super nice I just
wish they live somewhere
else the other day one of them brought
home some cookies from crumble you guys
know crumble the the the cookie Bakery
yeah all right we got some crumble love
love and they'll do like a a different
themed cookie right each week and she
brought home one and the flavor was
breast cancer
awareness and I was like that's kind of
weird right one
because I feel like everybody is already
aware of cancer we did it but two
I don't know what crumble is hoping to
achieve here because let's say somebody
didn't know about
cancer I don't think they should find
out through a
cookie imagine they walk into crumble
they're like this one looks good how
come the chips are pink and the worker's
like have you heard of
cancer it's a
disease enjoy your
treat I don't know I don't think that
baked goods are the best vehicle for
delivering terrible
news imagine if I went home and my
parents gave me a piece of cake and I
said thank you so much why is it black
and they were
like Grandpa's
dead funerals next week
bone
Appetit doesn't make sense why are we
having
dessert how many people found out about
covid through any
eclair I just don't get it I also think
it's weird because I feel like the
researchers and the oncologists they're
like we're trying to find a cure we need
money we need
resources and a cookie company is like
respectfully
we
disagree we think a Baker's Dozen could
really move the needle on
this and to me that kind of feels like
the edible version of thoughts and
prayers I think the weirdest thing to me
though about all this is
that cancer always gets the spotlight
and there's a lot of diseases out there
some diseases are even more lethal than
cancer in the US for example another top
10 killer in America is
diabetes and funny
enough crumble has not said a
[Applause]
thing they're not like try our diabetes
awareness
cookie death by chocolate
bring your own
insulin I think it's very
suspicious I don't know what crumble
thinks happens when I eat one of their
40,000 calorie
cookies but it doesn't make me feel
motivated to make a difference in the
world at that
moment it makes me feel
sick I wouldn't say cancer sick but
definitely diabetes sick
I don't
know I served a Mormon Mission I grew up
Mormon everyone knows the missionaries
right they go everywhere in pairs
they've got those little black name tags
and when they come to your home you
pretend not to be
there but I did that I served a mission
and as missionaries every day we go door
too and we would ask people can we teach
you about our
religion and believe it or not most
people say
no and what we would do as like a Hail
Mary when people turned us down is offer
to sing them A
Hymn in
hindsight offering to sing
Acappella for someone someone who has
just rejected speaking normally to
you is pretty
bizarre okay people were not taking
issue with how we were delivering our
message it was just a
message but I was like oh you don't
think Joseph Smith was a
prophet well what if I said Joseph Smith
was a prophet through music
then I think you'll be singing a
different
tune it was a weird tactic and it didn't
really
work imagine if a Salesman came to my
house and he said hey do you need pest
control and I was like no I'm good no
thank you and he was
like well can I sing something
the itsy bitsy spider called up
[Applause]
the doesn't make
sense and to be honest I don't think
that the singing was helping our
cause right because I have a hunch that
a lot of people think Mormons are a bit
odd
in US showing up to people's homes
Uninvited to sing ballads about
Mormonism was not
helping people were like
[Music]
confirmed they're super
weird they are theater kids but
Christian
[Music]
so the worst
variety but I serve my mission in El
Salvador and you don't get to pick where
you go right you're signed and when I
was called there I didn't really think
anything of it I was just excited but in
retrospect it is kind of crazy that they
sent us there because if you're not
familiar El Salvador is extremely
dangerous up until pretty recently it
had the number one murder rate in the
entire world
and I
personally cannot imagine a group of
people less
equipped to live in a violent gang Rong
country than Mormon
teenagers I had never seen an R-rated
movie
before in the church was
like you're going to be in one now
[Applause]
they're like don't worry though we're
going to send you to the Missionary
Training Center first and I was like I
need to learn how to
fight I play the piano in the organ give
me a knife I don't
know and they're like no no it's going
to be fine we're going to send you to
the Missionary Training Center for 6
weeks you're going to learn how to speak
Spanish
[Laughter]
and how to teach the
gospel and I was like oh that's perfect
that's good because my number one
concern with the murderous
gang was the language
barrier so that's
reassuring but it is really hard to be a
missionary because like like I was
saying every day you have to approach
complete strangers in the street in the
grocery store in their home
everywhere and just start talking to
them and starting that conversation
always felt very awkward and unnatural
and I never got very good at it but one
topic I did learn to avoid
was
religion specifically the the Mormon
religion people didn't love
it I did feel bad at times though being
in El Salvador I felt like I was maybe
an imposition I guess just because like
I was saying it's extremely dangerous
there and so people's lives are very
stressful and I felt like they had
bigger fish to fry than talking to me
like I remember I was teaching this one
guy one
day and he said to me during our lesson
I cannot leave my house the Gang has
told me that they will kill me so I'm
good here but if I leave my home I'm
literally a dead
man and I was
like that is not
good and you know what else is not good
coffee you guys that's it for me thank
you so much it's